Guide to the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images, 1889-2019 UPG.RG.60
ULS Greensburg
University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg, Visual Images
1889-2019
ULS Greensburg
University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
UPG.RG.60
60 Linear Feet
Visual Images from the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Campus.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Custodial History
Transferred from the UPG Administration to the UPG Archives.
Scope and Content Notes
Compact Discs, DVDs, Flash Drives, Negatives, Prints, Slides, Video Cassettes
Universities and colleges -- Pennsylvania -- Greensburg -- Records and correspondence; Universities and colleges -– Pennsylvania -– Greensburg -– Administration; University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg
- Compact Disc (CD), 1889-2010; I.
  - CD 1.A-N, 1889-2010; 1.
    Scope and Content Notes
    UPG Visual History.
    The collection contains selected images from the UPG Archives of the University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg and the Westmoreland County Historical Society. The images included are part of a larger collection of papers, artifacts, prints, slides, negatives, and videos documenting the history of the UPG campus. UPG was established in 1963.
    [CD 1.A-L,N Images; CD 1.M, Meta Data]
    - CD 1.A-N, 1889-2010 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 1)
- DVD (DVD), 2006-2019; II.
  - DVD 1, March 23-25, 2006; 1.
    "Medea" by Euripides. Translation by Ian Johnston, Malaspina University – College Nanaimo, BC, Canada. Choral ode text by Steven Schrum. Original music composed by Jade Shames except choral odes music by Amie Millward. University Theater Dept. Production [University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Theatre Company. Mar. 23-25, 2006.
    See Also
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. 2006, Mar. 23-25 Medea.
    - DVD 1, March 23-25, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 7)
  - DVD 2, June 16-17, 2006; 2.
    "Immaculate Misconceptions." A Monologue Performance by Stephen A. Schrum, Special Musical Guest Jeremy dePrisco. June 16 and 17, 2006, 8 p.m., Ferguson Theater, UPG Campus.
    See: UPG.RG.61 for CD "Immaculate Misconceptions music by Jeremy dePrisco from the play by Stephen Schrum." Blue Buddah Records BLBU5 c2006 Jeremy dePrisco. See also: UPG.RG.51 Biographical Files—Schrum, Dr. Stephen A. and dePrisco, Jeremy. See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Productions. 2006/07 Season. "Immaculate Misconceptions."
    - DVD 2, June 16-17, 2006 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 7)
  - DVD 3, 2006-2019; 3.
    DVD 3A 2006, Oct. 11 (7th) Tokar, Dr. Franklin K. "A Magnet for Good Architecture: The Laurel Hill Highlands from Mason House to Fallingwater and Beyond." 7th annual Arthur St. Clair Lectureship, Oct. 11, 2006, Ferguson Theater. Dr. Franklin K. Tokar is a professor in the History of Art and Architecture Department at the University of Pittsburgh, Oakland Campus.
    DVD3B 2007, Oct. 10 (8th) Mosher, Dr. Anne "Westmoreland's Downtown Heritage, From the Gilded Age to the Disney Era." 8th annual St. Clair Lectureship, October 10, 2007, Ferguson theater. Dr. Anne Mosher, Professor of Geography, Syracuse University.
    DVD3C 2010, Oct. 6 (11th) Cannadine, Sir David "Andrew W. Mellon: Making Money & Giving It Away." 11th Annual St. Clair Lectureship, October 6, 2010. Ferguson Theater. Sir David Cannadine, British scholar, historian and author of Mellon: An American Life.
    DVD3D 2011, Oct. 12 (12th) Nasaw, David, PhD "Making Sense of Making Millions". 12th Annual Arthur St. Clair Lectureship, October 12, 2011, Ferguson Theater. David Nasaw, PhD, author of the Pulitzer Prize for Biography finalist Andrew Carnegie and a distinguished professor of American History at Graduate Center of the City University of New York and director for the Humanities at the City University of New York. See also: RG52 Subject Files. Ser.: [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    DVD3E Oct. 10, 2012 (13th) "Remembering the Battle of Bushy Run; Decisive Victory of Minor Skirmish" with Frank A. Cassell, PhD, 13th Annual St. Clair Lecture, Oct. 10, 2012. DVD 1 hr 30 min.
    DVD3F 2013, Oct. 21 (14th) "Emancipating Lincoln: The Prose and Poetry of the Emancipation Proclamation" by Harold Holzer, the Metropolitan Museum of Art senior vice president for external affairs and a leading authority on Abraham Lincoln and the political culture of the Civil War era. 2 copies.
    DVD3G 2014, Oct. 16 (15th) "Was the 'Whiskey Rebellion' Really About Whiskey?" by Terry Bouton, Assoc. Prof. of History, University of Maryland, Baltimore, MD where he is a Presidential Teaching Professor and an Organization of American Historians Distinguished Lecturer.
    DVD3H 2015, Oct. 15 (16th) "Pennsylvania's Role in Presidential Politics -- Past and Present" by G. Terry Madonna, PhD, Prof. of Public Affairs, Franklin and Marshall College.
    DVD3I 2016, Nov. 29 (17th) [lecture originally scheduled for Oct. 13] "Bouquets from the Cannon's Mouth: Soldiering with the Eighth Regiment of the Pennsylvania Reserve" by Robert E. Eberly, Jr., JD.
    DVD3J 2019, Feb. 5 (18th) "Arthur S. Clair: Myth and History" by Susan Sommers, PhD.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: [Arthur] St. Clair Lectureship.
    - DVD 3, 2006-2019 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8, Shelf 7)
  - DVD 4, February 2-4, 2007; 4.
    Greensburg American Opera Company (Christina Farrell, Found Director) Presents "The Telephone" by Gian Carlo Menotti & "The Impressario" by W. A. Mozart. Stage Direction by Dr. Stephen A. Schrum, Musical Direction by Maestro Efrain Amaya. February 2-4, 2007 in the Pitt-Greensburg Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. 2006/07 Season. Greensburg American Opera Co.
    - DVD 4, February 2-4, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 5A (Act 1), DVD 5B (Act 2), March 29-31, 2007; 5.
    "Mother Courage and Her Children" by Bertolt Brecht and featuring original music composed for the show by Pitt @ Greensburg students Ashley Peer, Chad Smith and Eric Durant. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company, Spring, 2007.
    - DVD 5A (Act 1), DVD 5B (Act 2), March 29-31, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 6, January 22, 2007 - January 17, 2008; 6.
    La Cultura Lecture Series.
    2007. "Visions of China": DVD6.A.1, Jan. 22, 2007, Dr. Monte Broaded, Director of International Programs at Butler University, "Does a Rising Tide Lift All Boats? Economic Growth and Inequality in China"; DVD6.A.2, Feb. 12, 2007, Poet Huang Xiang of the North Side of Pittsburgh, "A Beast Drinking Wildly But Not Drunk".
    2008. "Egypt: Crossroads of Civilization": DVD6.B.1, Sept. 28, 2007, Dr. Christina Michelmore, Chatham Univ., "A Historical Overview – Yesterday and Today."; DVD 6.B.2, Jan. 17, 2008, Khawala Kittaneh, Indiana University of Pa., "Explore Islam: An introduction to the basic teachings and how these teachings promote peace and respect for other religions and sacredness of human life".
    N.B. For video cassettes of La Cultura Lecture Series for 2002, 2003, 2004, 2006, See: UPG.RG.60.VC VIII.15-18.
    - DVD 6, January 22, 2007 - January 17, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 7, 2007-2019; 7.
    University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg Commencement 2007 (DVD 7.1) 2008 (DVD 7.2) 2009 (DVD 7.3) 2010 (DVD 7.4) 2011 (DVD 7.5) 2012 (DVD 7.6) 2013 (DVD 7.7) 2014 (DVD 7.8) 2015 (DVD 7.9) 2016 (DVD 7.10) 2017 (DVD 7.11) 2018 (DVD 7.12) 2019 (DVD 7.13)
    n.b.: For videocassettes of Commencements 1990-2006, See: UPG.RG.60.VC V.1-15, 17.
    - DVD 7, 2007-2019 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 8, November 13, 2007; 8.
    Mary Lou Campana Chapel [and Lecture Center] Dedication Ceremony. Tuesday, November 13, 2007.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Buildings—Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center. See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Programs (Dedication)—Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center.
    - DVD 8, November 13, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 9A (Act 1), DVD 9B (Act 2), November 15-17, 2007; 9.
    "The House of Blue Leaves" by John Guare. Music and Lyrics by John Guare, Directed by Stephen A. Schrum. Presented by The Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company. UPG Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. 2007/08 "The House of Blue Leaves."
    - DVD 9A (Act 1), DVD 9B (Act 2), November 15-17, 2007 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 10A, DVD 10B, April 3-5, 2008; 10.
    "The Miser" by Moliere. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company. UPG Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2007/2008. "The Miser."
    - DVD 10A, DVD 10B, April 3-5, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 11A, DVD 11B, November 20-22, 2008; 11.
    "An Evening of One Acts" ("Life Line" by Douglas Craven; "Hard Candy" by Jonathan Rand; "Actor's Nightmare" by Christopher Durang; "4:48 Psychosis is" by Sarah Kane.) UPG Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2008/2009, "An Evening of One Acts."
    - DVD 11A, DVD 11B, November 20-22, 2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 12A, DVD 12B, April 2-4, 2009; 12.
    "Wonder of the World" by David Lindsay-Abaire, Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company, Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2008/09, "Wonder of the World."
    - DVD 12A, DVD 12B, April 2-4, 2009 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 13, November 19-21, 2009; 13.
    "The Duchess of Malfi" by John Webster. The Pitt Greensburg Theatre Company, Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2009/2010, "The Duchess of Malfi."
    - DVD 13, November 19-21, 2009 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 14A, DVD 14B (Act 2), March 24-27, 2010; 14.
    [Warning: the disc 2 menus are not correct]
    "Urinetown, the Musical." Music by Mark Hollman, Lyrics by Mark Hollman & Greg Kotis, Book by Greg Kotis. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company, Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2009/2010. "Urinetown, the Musical."
    - DVD 14A, DVD 14B (Act 2), March 24-27, 2010 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 15A, DVD 15B, November 18-20, 2010; 15.
    "Play it Again, Sam" by Woody Allen. The Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Co., Ferguson Theater.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions, Season 2010/2011, "Play it Again, Sam."
    - DVD 15A, DVD 15B, November 18-20, 2010 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 16, April 1-2, 2011; 16.
    "You Can't Take It With You", Kaufman & Hart. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company, Spring 2011.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions, Season 2010/2011, "You Can't Take It With You."
    - DVD 16, April 1-2, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 17, 2006 - 2019; 17.
    Cobetto Lecture Series [Dr. Bernard H. Cobetto Lecture Series on Ethics]
    2006. (1st.) Randy Cohen. "How to Be Good." [No DVD of this lecture is in the Archives.]
    2007, (2nd), Dr. James Childress, "Just Care: Rationing in a Public Health Care Crisis."
    2008, (3rd.). Dr. Everette E. Dennis, "Trusting the Media in a Presidential Year: Can We or Not--A look at Freedom of the press in the digital Age." [No DVD of this lecture is in the Archives.]
    2009, (4th), Dr. Barbara M. Porco, "Ethical Leadership: The Tipping Point in a Financial Crisis."
    2010, (5th). Paul H. O'Neil. "The Role of a Leader in Creating a Values-Based Institution."
    2011, (6th), Dr. Bernard Duberstein, "Leadership Lessons from the Oval Office and the Board Room."
    2012, (7th), Dr. John E. Abraham, "Madmen, Educats, and Demagogues: Confessions of a Recovering Politician."
    2013, (8th), Dr. Wendy Lynne Lee, "When the Earth Moves Under Our Feet; The Pennsylvania Marcellus Gas Rush."
    2014, (9th), "End-of-Life-Care issue", A Panel Discussion featuring: Robert Arnold, MD; Helen Burns, PhD, RN, FAAN; John Dickson IV; Alan Meisel, Esq.
    2015, (10th), "Toward an Ethics of Love & Hope: Five Transformative Ideas" with William Rued, PhD.
    2016, (11th), Joanne Katz, JD "Restorative Justice: Exploring Ethics and Criminal Justice in the Age of Mass Incarceration." [No DVD of this lecture in Archives.]
    2017, (12th), William Chess, retired COO, Oglivy Public Relations World, "Public Relations: Public Policy and Crisis Communications in a World That Relies on Social Media."
    2018, (13th). Panel discussion, "Sexual Misconduct: Perspectives on the Problem, Possibilities for Resolution." [No DVD of this lecture in Archives.]
    2019, (14th), Panel discussion, "Climate Change & Its Effect on Western Pennsylvania."
    - DVD 17, 2006 - 2019 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 18, 18.
    "Fall One Acts: Thirst" by Eugene O'Neill; "The Spurt of Blood" by Antonin Artaud. Directed by Elliot Sheedy. Free Admission. 7:30 p.m. Oct. 13th and 14th, Ferguson Theater; Oct. 15th, West 2nd Street Gallery. A Performing Arts Society Production sponsored by SGA.
    - DVD 18 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 19, October 28, 2011; 19.
    "Broadway Battles Breast Cancer". A Benefit Concert for the Breast Cancer Research Foundation. Friday, Oct. 28, [2011]. 7:30 p.m. UPG Campana Chapel, University of Pittsburgh at Greensburg. Sponsored by Performing Arts Society.
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: Programs (Miscellaneous). "Broadway Battles Breast Cancer."
    - DVD 19, October 28, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 20, November 17-20, 2011; 20.
    "Hippolytus" Euripides. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company. November 2011. [November 17-20].
    See also: UPG Archives UPG.RG.52 Ser.: Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2011/12. "Hippolytus."
    - DVD 20, November 17-20, 2011 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 21A, DVD 21B, March 24-26, 2012; 21.
    "Dog Assassin". The World Premier of a New Musical. Book & Lyrics by Stephen Schrum. Music by Jeremy DePrisco. Ferguson Theater. [Act 1, DVD 21A; Act 2, DVD 21B].
    See also, UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2012/2013 "Dog Assassin."
    - DVD 21A, DVD 21B, March 24-26, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 22, December 1-2, 2011; 22.
    "Promethus Bound" by Aeschylus. [A blended reality event performed in the online 3D world of Second Life. UPG Ferguson Theater].
    See also: UPG.RG.52 UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2011/12 for additional information.
    - DVD 22, December 1-2, 2011 (Microfilm-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD [DVD+R] 23, June 15, 2012; 23.
    Retrospective; Retirees: Joyce Bucchi, Elizabeth (Bea) Cox, Karen Gavula, Virginia (Ginny) Kemerer, William (Bill) Martin, Daniel (Dan) Mudry, Joseph (Joe) Olczak, Rebecca Sorice. [Disc contains photos of the 30 June 2012 retirees at various events and stages of their career during their individual respective careers at UPG.] Presented at the retirement reception on 15 June 2012 Hempfield Room, Chambers Hall.
    - DVD [DVD+R] 23, June 15, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 24, 1983-2008; 24.
    n.b. The contents of the 15 DVD video discs which constitute UPG Archives UPG.RG.60.DVD.24 UPG Campus History were transferred from 27 UPG Archives VHS tapes on 6/4/12. See: UPG Archives UPG.RG.60.VC (Videocassettes). [faz]
    DVD 24A Oral History of UPG. Interviews. (9 DVD Video Discs) 1994-2002
    DVD 24A.1 Mary Lynch Quinn 7/26/94
    DVD 24A.2 Dr. Norman McWhinney 5/21/97
    DVD 24A.3 Dr. Guy Nicoletti 5/28/97
    DVD 24A.4 Dr. Paul Chew 6/4/97
    DVD 24A.5 Dr. Carl Poke 6/18/97
    DVD 24A.6 Dr. Norman Scanlon 6/24/97
    DVD 24A.7 Dr. Donald Reilly 7/6/97
    DVD 24A.8 Dr. Guy Rossetti 7/20/98, 1/25/99 [Guy Rossetti Memorial Commemoration]
    DVD 24A.9 Dr. George F. Chambers 8/1/02, 10/11/02
    DVD 24B Events (5 DVD Video Discs) 1983-2002
    DVD 24.B.1 Cultura, La. Dinner and Reception. "The Life and Times of Leonardo da Vinci. 2002
    DVD 24B.2 Fall Festival. 1983 (Track #1); 1991 (Track #2)
    DVD 24B.3 Humanities Day. 1983. (Track 1, Program of Events; Track 2, Candid Shots); 1996 (Track 3); 1997 (Track 4)
    DVD 24B.4 Honors Convocation. 4th, 2000 (Track #1); Graduation [Commencement.] 2nd, 1990. (Track #2)
    DVD 24B.5 Granada, Forum on Issues Relating to, November 11, 1983. Guest Speakers: Dr. Richard Blackett, Professor of History and Black Studies, University of Pittsburgh Oakland and a Caribbean Specialist; Dr. Donald Gibson, Assistant Professor of Sociology, UPG; Russell Rowe, Editorial Editor of the UPG student newspaper. Participant: J. Vollmer.
    DVD 24C Dedication Ceremonies (1 DVD Video Disc)August 22, 1988 - May 14, 2008
    Track 1 Chambers Hall (Renaming of Common Facilities Bldg. to Chambers Hall) 6/20/97
    Track 2 Carillon (Ferguson Carillion: The Edith Ferguson Chambers Carillon) 9/9/95. Children's Collection (The Joan Chambers Children's Collection) 9/9/95
    Track 3 Clock (Campus Clock) 10/13/95
    Track 4 Robertshaw Hall 8/22/88
    Track 5 Millstein Library (Fanny K. Millstein Library) 5/5/95
    Track 6 "Upward to the Light". The Dr. Albert Paul Chew Memorial Window. Millstein Library. 5/14/2008
    - DVD 24, 1983-2008 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 25, September 5, 2012; 25.
    [UPG] Frank A. Cassell Hall Ribbon Cutting Ceremony.
    - DVD 25, September 5, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 26, November 15-18, 2012; 26.
    "Arsenic and Old Lace" by Joseph Kesselring. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2012/2013 "Arsenic and Old Lace."
    - DVD 26, November 15-18, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 27, April 4-5, 2013; 27.
    "Eleanor, and American Love Story". Pitt-Theater & Music Company Production. [2 copies]
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser. UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2012/2013 "Eleanor, and American Love Story."
    - DVD 27, April 4-5, 2013 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 28, Fall 2013; 28.
    The Birth of Merlin [Promo Videos] Nov. 2013. [On YouTube: http://youtu.be/dDbe3dJ86n8; http://youtu.be/-NBAJRYUQyu.]
    DVD 28A [Performance] "The Birth of Merlin". Fall, 2013.
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 3013/2014. The Birth of Merlin.
    - DVD 28, Fall 2013 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 29, 29.
    "Pussy Riot: a Punk Prayer." n.b.: Public Performance Rights for the Pitt-Greensburg Campus only. Another circulating copy is available in the Carl Poke Media Collection.
    - DVD 29 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 30A (Act 1), DVD 30B (Act 2), April 3-5, 2014; 30.
    "A Very Potter Musical" ["A Night of Music" featuring A "A Very Potter Musical"]. Pitt-Greensburg Theatre Company, Ferguson Theater.
    - DVD 30A (Act 1), DVD 30B (Act 2), April 3-5, 2014 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 31, April 14, 2014; 31.
    "Cabaret" [2014]. Ferguson Theater. The Pitt-Greensburg Performing Arts Society annual Cabaret showcases the talent of the campus' students, faculty, and staff.
    - DVD 31, April 14, 2014 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 32A, DVD 32B, January 31, 2015; 32.
    DVD 32A Estrada (Florez-Estrada), Dr. Nancy B. Memorial Service, Saturday, January 31, 2015, 3:00 p.m., Mary Lou Campana Chapel and Lecture Center.
    DVD 32B Estrada, (Florez-Estrada), Dr. Nancy B. Memorial Service. Powerpoint. Slide images used at Janurary 31, 2015 Memorial Service.
    - DVD 32, January 31, 2015 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 33A, DVD 33B, April 7-10, 2016; 33.
    "Man of LaMancha". Pitt-Greensburg Theater Company. Ferguson Theater. DVD 33A (Act 1); DVD 33B (Act 2).
    - DVD 33A, DVD 33B, April 7-10, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 34, May 6, 2016; 34.
    David Conrad, Keynote Speaker, Pitt-Greensburg Humanities Day.
    - DVD 34, May 6, 2016 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 35, 2014/2015; 35.
    "Chemical Imbalance: A Jekyll and Hyde Play."
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2014/2015. "Chemical Imbalance: A Jekyll and Hyde Play."
    - DVD 35, 2014/2015 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 36, 2016/2017; 36.
    "Shakespeare in Hollywood."
    See also: UPG.RG.52 Ser.: UPG Theater Dept. Productions. Season 2016/2017. "Shakespeare in Hollywood."
    - DVD 36, 2016/2017 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 37, April 15, 2009; 37.
    UPG Chorale [Pitt Greensburg Chorale] Pitt Greensburg Chorale Concert.
    - DVD 37, April 15, 2009 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD 38 [DVD-R], February 25, 2012; 38.
    Panther Leadership Summit [Hosted by the University of Pittsburgh Division of Student Services. Since its inception the summit has been a convenient, affordable means of providing University of Pittsburgh and Pittsburgh Council of Higher Education (PCHE) consortium students with high quality leadership training and development]
    6th Annual Panther Leadership Summit.
    - DVD 38 [DVD-R], February 25, 2012 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
  - DVD (Miscellaneous), September 11, 2001; 39.
    World Trade Center Tribute.
    See: UPG.RG.52 Subject Files. Ser.: World Trade Center, Terrorist Attack on, September 11, 2001.
    - DVD (Miscellaneous), September 11, 2001 (Museum-cabinet 4, Shelf 8)
- Flash Drive (FD), 2009-2018; III.
  - FD 1, 2009-2011; 1.
    Contains:
    Fitness Center [UPG Fitness Center]. Construction. 2009. Interior/Exterior. 11 images
    College Hall. Graduate Room. Interior. 3 images.
    Wildlife [UPG Wildlife]. Turtle. 2009. See also: UPG.RG.60 Prints. Wildlife [UPG Wildlife]. Mallards.
    RA [Resident Assistant] Training Fall 09 10 images: image 1: Alicia Kania; John Ritenour; image 2: B. Kertoy; M. Krzanowski; image 3: Hoffman & Woloszyki; image 4: Justin Carter; image 5: Kristina Slifer; image 6: K. Slifer, A. Whitmer, K. Sadler; image 7: L. Solic; T. Ross, J. Ritenour, M. Hoffman; image 8: Maria Hoffman, Chris Weloszyk; image 9: M. Hoffman, T. Horan; image 10: RA Training 09 [Resident Assistants Group Photo].
    UPG Campus Winter 2010 4 images of campus winter scenes during the snowiest recorded February (48.9 inches).
    Construction Projects 2010. UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress photos. 10/14/10. 22 images. For prints, see Oversize UPG.RG.60 Construction Projects 2010. Softball Field.
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress photos. 10/28/10. 21 images. For prints, see Oversize UPG.RG.60 Construction Projects 2010. Softball Field.
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4941. Progress Photos. 10/28/10. 8 images. For prints, see Oversize UPG.RG.60 Construction Projects 2010. Baseball Field.
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4941. Progress Photos. 11/11/10. 14 images. For prints, see Oversize UPG.RG.60 Construction Projects 2010. Baseball Field.
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4647. Progress Photos. 11/11/10. 40 images. n.b.: No prints made from Flash Drive for this date. [faz 11/18/10]
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress Photos. 2/11/11. 15 images. Images on FD only. [faz 2/17/11]
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4941. Progress Photos. 4/7/11. 105 images. Images on FD only. [faz]
    UPG Baseball Field. Baseball Field Reclamation Project. IMG00201-20110415-1344jpg. [4/15?/11]
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress Photos. 6/23/11 20 images.
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4941. Progress Photos. 6/23/11 21 images.
    UPG Baseball Field. Job X4941. Final Photos. 7/25?/11 29 images.
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress Photos. 8/4/11 8 images.
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. Progress Photos. 8/18/11 21 images.
    UPG Basball Field. Job X4941. Final Photos. 8/18/11 5 images.
    UPG Softball Field. Job X4647. [Progress] Photos. 12/15/11 7 images.
    - FD 1, 2009-2011 (Museum-cabinet 3, Shelf 1, Box 1)
  - FD 2, 2005-2013; 2.
    University of Pittsburgh Financial Disclosure Reports. [Note: UPG Archives holdings of the electronic editions begin with 2008/2009; for previous print editions, see RG70.2 UPO DOC [year] FIN] UPG Archives holdings in electronic format: 2008/2009; 2009/2010; 2010/2011, 2011/2012, 2012/2013.